<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="chat_title_style_g">Chat title style</string>
    <string name="unread_at_top_g">Unread always at the top</string>
    <string name="show_sim_selection_dialog">Show SIM card selection dialog when sending</string>
    <string name="delete_after_copy">Delete message after copying number from notification</string>
    <string name="sound_on_out_going_messages">Sound on out going messages</string>
    <string name="delivered">Delivered</string>
    <string name="failed">Failed</string>
    <string name="pending">Pending</string>
    <string name="message_type">Message type</string>
    <string name="show_number_in_title">Show number in title</string>
    <string name="warning_disclosure">
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>Data Access Disclosure</h2>

<p><strong>This app requires access to SMS messages and phone-related information to function properly.</strong></p>

<h3>🔍 What Information We Access:</h3>
<ul>
    <li><strong>SMS MESSAGES:</strong> Full content of your SMS messages.</li>
    <li><strong>YOUR PHONE NUMBER(S):</strong> The phone number(s) associated with your device\'s SIM card(s).</li>
    <li><strong>PHONE NUMBERS FROM SMS:</strong> Phone numbers contained within your SMS messages.</li>
</ul>

<h3>📱 How We Use This Information (LOCALLY ON DEVICE):</h3>
<ul>
    <li><strong>YOUR PHONE NUMBER:</strong> We <strong>collect and use</strong> your device\'s phone number <strong>only to display it</strong> in the app interface for SIM card selection. <em>This number is processed locally and not transmitted.</em></li>
    <li><strong>PHONE NUMBERS FROM SMS:</strong> We <strong>extract phone numbers</strong> from SMS messages to allow you to copy them easily. <em>This extraction happens locally.</em></li>
    <li><strong>SMS CONTENT FOR OTP:</strong> We <strong>analyze SMS text</strong> to automatically detect and copy OTP codes to your clipboard. <em>This analysis happens locally.</em></li>
</ul>

<h3>🚫 What We DO NOT Do With Your Data:</h3>
<ul>
    <li><strong>We do NOT TRANSMIT or UPLOAD</strong> your SMS messages, phone numbers, or any message content to any server.</li>
    <li><strong>We do NOT STORE</strong> your SMS data or phone numbers on external servers.</li>
    <li><strong>We do NOT SHARE</strong> your personal data with third parties.</li>
</ul>

<h3>✅ Key Guarantee:</h3>
<p><strong>All data processing occurs exclusively on your device (on-device).</strong> Your SMS messages and phone numbers never leave your device. Internet access is used only for sending MMS and processing Google Play purchases.</p>

<h3>🔑 Required Permissions Explained:</h3>
<ul>
    <li><strong>READ_SMS:</strong> To access SMS for OTP copying and phone number extraction (local processing only).</li>
    <li><strong>READ_PHONE_STATE:</strong> To collect and display your device\'s phone number for SIM selection (local use only).</li>
</ul>

<p><em>By continuing, you acknowledge that:</em></p>
<ol>
    <li>This app collects your device\'s phone number for local display</li>
    <li>This app accesses SMS messages for local OTP and phone number extraction</li>
    <li>None of this data is transmitted from your device</li>
</ol>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="restricted_settings_guide">Android has restricted access to SMS features for this app. To continue:\n\n1. Tap \"OK\" to open App Settings.\n2. Tap the three dots (⋮) in the top right corner.\n3. Select \"Allow restricted settings\".\n4. Return to the app and try again.</string>
</resources>
